The moment, especially until the early morning,
we're first 2021.
We have the invitation to chapter the one church,
sir, you know.
Let's go to the one where our Father, our God,
we thank you so much, Father, for the free and the way you joy
and his country, God and the thank you for the city.
His leadership, God, and the thank you for the Republic
that we share together.
God, and the giving the opportunity to vote for these individuals who are
making decisions, kind of give them wisdom, kind of give them discernment,
to find their will for our great city, God,
for being able to live here to enjoy our dreams together.
But thank for our friends, our family, Jesus, and we do pray.
Amen.
I think it is to be like the United States of America,
and to be a republic for the state, my nation, and the God,
and the United States of America, and the United States of Scotland.
We are more of a good book, it's given personal gratitude,
but we send it to goodness that, and if you're kind of six,
to make it two, two, two, two, three, four, five.
Next, I, Father.
Amen.
No state to be in the middle of the region, the vision one,
and the jail to be in.
So what you have got in your packet is the product of many months of work,
but staff, you're trying to modify this position,
but there was an accurate packet that we've seen.
There was a such a good amount of discussion
with the committee issues that we had last year.
This was presented to the mayor's citizens,
cooperative advisory committee last week,
and in fact, the approval of everybody there,
the main change of what we're doing with this proposed change
is, as the ordinance brings right now,
if somebody wants to pay our utility bill,
if it's not there, they're statement,
if you can't number one of the other identifiers
that we require them there to be charged with five dollar fee.
The person is only there to pay off my account,
because it doesn't make a whole lot of sense.
It's the point of that fee,
making sure that the money goes.
And so the person who did not identify my address or other reads were a suspect.
So the main change in this is that if somebody is there to pay on multiple accounts and doesn't have the information information.
Partly, evidence for why this was treated in place, in the end of the client's hold, is the whole client.
But somebody being in a pay-on multiple accounts didn't know we could count numbers.
So it was divided up as best they could figure out how to apply to that.
Well, they didn't took the money to pay for your account.
So it's some kind of a pre-sherical feat.
That residents were, whatever's not paid, that should have all been submitted by the pre-sherical.
So the whole point of the decision to see that payments are accurately applied to the accounts as the person paying the bill.
That should have worked.
The best that we're going to weigh is about our charge or individual.
It's going to be about our charge, but that's to people who don't know.
Yes, there are some exceptions.
And the reason for those exceptions.
So it's something that's been many in the Dropbox.
Somebody that's made a nuclear payment.
Somebody that trying to remember what all the exceptions were.
But the reason for those is because on shutoff day, we get a whole bunch of payments that are made by means of it.
We can talk with it and try to figure out how to specify what we can do.
Well, we had to go through the process of trying to figure out where this money is supposed to go.
When they put money in the Dropbox with the bill at the end, it would delay our shelves by such a length of time.
That we probably wouldn't get the shelves until the end.
Whereas we tried to get the shelves in the morning so that they have all that convenient to do with this.
So we can go back and turn it back on if they need things.
So there are exceptions.
But we figured that your lots of this decision is the most practical way of trying to resolve this.
And then the theory is to go.
Sorry for changing the rate of the charges or, okay, so, by hand,
the system has the right to ask for a rebate on their breeder.
It is accurate.
We will charge them a rebate, the cost of rolling at least a quick amount there, which is $95.
You have, and it just wasn't real leaders how we end that he used to be in a pot.
This is just to make it a little weird.
The rebate shows that our original rebate was correct or consistent with the amount of the usage that we see when we go through the rebate,
and the rebate, that they are charged at the fee, that it is not consistent.
They haven't still at that point.
They haven't used the amount of electricity to be able to amount of water.
They are willing to afford it.
Then we play the rebate fee, and adjust their bill according to whether you can get it.
That was simply not really spelled that in the old works.
That this means that you are approval, then you have to fit this on the initial,
or a city council agenda, as I can say not, but you can actually put it on the board.
So this is a government, it's even established by a government, so it has to be a lot of pot of pot of water.
Or that's the best that I see the answer to.
Fine, I see.
Go ahead and take the answer there.
No need to take the answer here, if you would take action and send the answer.
No, we're doing anything other than doing business for the rest of all these things.
I'm so excited to do it.
Hello, staff of the works.
12 trustee community of council.
15, my turn.
Over to you.
Again.
Hi.